valorebooks.com 2008-09-12

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

Collegiate Marketplace LLC knows that information you share with us is sensitive and private. We attempt to use that information carefully and sensibly. This notice describes our privacy policy. 

By visiting Collegiate Marketplace LLC, you accept the practices described in this Privacy Policy. 

Personal Information That Collegiate Marketplace LLC Gathers 

The information you supply us allows us to personalize and improve your experience with Collegiate Marketplace LLC. Here are the types of information we gather. 

* Information You Give Us: We receive and store information you enter on our Web site or give us in any other way. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing shopping features, improving our services and communicating with you. 

* Automatic Information: We store certain information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many Web sites, we use "cookies," so when your Web browser accesses Collegiate Marketplace LLC, it stores certain information about you. 

* Information from Other Sources: We might receive information about you from other sources and add it to our account information. 

Examples of Information Collected 

Information You Give Us: You provide most such information when you use our services, participate in a contest or questionnaire or communicate with customer service. As a result, you might supply us with such information as your name, address, phone numbers and e-mail addresses; credit/debit card or other payment information; people to whom purchases have been shipped, including their addresses, phone numbers and e-mail addresses; content of reviews; personal descriptions and information about you; and financial information, including Social Security and driver's license numbers. 

Automatic Information: Examples of the information we collect and analyze include the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet; login; e-mail address; password; computer and connection information such as browser type, version, and time zone setting, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system, and platform; purchase history, which we sometimes aggregate with similar information from other customers to create certain features or to establish particular and generic customer profiles; the full Uniform Resource Locator (URL) clickstream to, through, and from our Web site, including date and time; cookie number; products you viewed or searched for; and the phone number you used to call our 800 number. 

We may also use browser data such as cookies, Flash cookies (also known as Flash Local Shared Objects), or similar data on certain parts of our Web site for fraud prevention and other purposes. During some visits we may use software tools such as JavaScript to measure and collect session information, including page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs), and methods used to browse away from the page. 

Information from Other Sources: Examples of information we receive from other sources include updated delivery and address information from our carriers or other third parties, which we use to correct our records and deliver your next purchase or communication more easily; account information, purchase or redemption information, and page-view information from some merchants with which we operate co-branded businesses or for which we provide technical, fulfillment, advertising or other services; search term and search result information from some searches conducted through the Web searches through our site; search results and links, including paid listings (such as sponsored links); and credit history information from credit bureaus, which we use to help prevent and detect fraud and to offer certain credit or financial services to some customers. 

Third-Party Advertisers and Links to Other Web Sites: Examples of third-party advertisers and advertising companies that you can link to from the Collegiate Marketplace LLC Web site or that serve advertising content directly to your browser on certain Collegiate Marketplace LLC pages. 

Information You Can Access: Examples of information you can access easily at Collegiate Marketplace LLC include up-to-date information regarding your orders; personally identifiable information (including name, e-mail, password and communications preferences); payment settings (including credit/debit card and other like information); e-mail notification settings; and your profile. 

Cookies 

* Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to provide certain features associated with our company. 

* The Help feature on the toolbar of most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie or how to disable cookies altogether. Also, you can disable or delete similar data used by browser add-ons, such as Flash cookies, by changing the add-on's settings or visiting the Web site of its manufacturer. However, cookies allow you to take full advantage of some of Collegiate Marketplace LLC's features, and we recommend that you leave them turned on. 

Information Sharing 

We are not in the business of selling information we acquire from our customers to others. We share customer information as described below and with our affiliates, and we strongly encourage anyone with whom we share this information with to follow this Privacy Policy or follow practices at least as protective as those described in it. 

* Third Party Service Providers: We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes. 

* Business Transfers: As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy other companies or business units. If we should do so, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets but remains subject to the promises made in any pre-existing privacy policy (including this one), unless, of course, the customer consents otherwise. Also, in the unlikely event that another company acquires Collegiate Marketplace LLC or substantially all of its assets, that company most likely would want to acquire our customer information. 

* Protection of Collegiate Marketplace LLC and Others: We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law; enforce or apply our other policies, including our Participation Agreement and conditions and guidelines that pertain to the use of our services and including those intended to protect the our rights, property or safety or those of others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. However, this does not include selling, renting, sharing or otherwise disclosing personally identifiable information from customers for commercial purposes in violation of the commitments set forth in this Privacy Policy. 

Security Measures 

The Internet has made it much easier to acquire personal information about others, and no matter what steps we take to protect information, there is no such thing as perfect security on the Internet. Still, we try to protect your information. For instance, we employ certain security techniques to protect such data from unauthorized access by users inside and outside our company. 

As part of our efforts, we use firewalls and SSL software: 

* Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software encrypts information you input and thus makes it harder for unauthorized persons to find out that information. 

* We reveal only the last four digits of your credit/debit card (or other payment account information) numbers when confirming an order. Of course, we transmit the entire credit card number to the appropriate credit/debit/other company during order processing. 

* It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer. 

Also, we may look across multiple users to identify problems or resolve disputes, and in particular we may examine your information to identify users using multiple user IDs or aliases. 

As well, although we employ SSL technology to keep your credit card information safe, and use encryption to protect transmitted data, and we will never pass your credit card number through e-mail, nonetheless, for your greater protection, we ask that even when purchasing with your saved credit card numbers, you enter the last four digits of the number. This measure protects your card number if you forget to sign off from our site after making a purchase. As we noted above, you can aid in keeping your personal information safe if you to sign off once you are finished using the site and close down the browser window if you are on a public or shared computer. 

In addition: 

1\. We will not sell or rent your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes and will only disclose your personal information in accordance with our Privacy Policy or with your explicit consent. 

2\. We discourage third parties from selling the information we provide to them, to market directly to you, or to disclose it in any other way without your explicit consent. As well, the law may afford you some legal protection against these third parties. 

3\. We share your personal information with our own service providers for our operations only to facilitate or outsource our services and operations, but only under confidentiality restrictions. 

4\. We disclose limited personal contact information to verified requests by law enforcement and government officials who conduct civil or criminal investigations, or where otherwise required or authorized by law. However, we do require a subpoena for additional personal information. 

5\. We allow you to change your personal information so that you can keep it current. 

We believe that the security and privacy measures that we take make Collegiate Marketplace LLC a secure place to shop, but unfortunately there are no guarantees. 

Choices 

* As discussed above, you can always choose not to provide information, even though you might need to supply that information to make a purchase or to take advantage of certain Collegiate Marketplace LLC features. 

* You can add or update certain information. When you update information, we usually keep a copy of the prior version for our records. 

Children & Collegiate Marketplace LLC 

Collegiate Marketplace LLC does not permit anyone who uses our Web site to sell products from or to a person who is less than 18 years of age without the involvement of that person's parent or guardian. 

As well, Collegiate Marketplace LLC does not permit anyone to post in any way any material that involves or appears to involve the sexual exploitation and other abuse of minors, whether or not such material is illegal. If you should find any such material, we strongly encourage you to report this to us immediately. 

Obligations, Revisions and Concerns 

If you visit Collegiate Marketplace LLC, whether or not you use Collegiate Marketplace LLC to buy or sell anything, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Use Conditions and Guidelines, including provisions in these documents that concern limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, infringement of state and federal laws dealing with privacy, intellectual property, sexually explicit material, offensive material, as well as to the laws of the United States and of the State of Delaware. If you are a seller, you will be subject to our Participation Agreement as well, and if you are a buyer, you may wish to read the Participation Agreement anyway for further information about Collegiate Marketplace LLC's policies, including those concerning privacy at Collegiate Marketplace LLC. 

If you have any questions about privacy at Collegiate Marketplace LLC, please contact us, give us a thorough description of the issue, and we will try to resolve your concerns. 

Since our business, the law and our sense of appropriate practices changes constantly, our Privacy Policy, the Participation Agreement, the Use Conditions and the Use Guidelines may change too. You should expect them to change. We may, or may not, e-mail periodic reminders of our notices and conditions, but in any case, you should check our Web site frequently to see recent changes. When Collegiate Marketplace LLC makes changes to this Privacy Policy, it will post them online. They will apply to all of our customers when posted, so they will bind you, whether or not you have otherwise expressly agreed to them. When you use our Web site, your use is your agreement to be bound by these changes. 

Last updated: August 1, 2008
